we all wish to be financially
independent and live without having to
rely on others for our needs and wants
but how do we ensure financial security
in this world of continuously
fluctuating markets and unstable
interest rates
how do we create a long-term source of
fixed income that is guaranteed and
unaffected by external circumstances
presenting the icici prove guaranteed
pension plan an annuity plan
that allows you to turn your savings
into financial security in the form of a
guaranteed lifelong income
[Music]
whether you are a working professional
who doesn't want to depend entirely on
your salary and is looking for an
alternate source of income
a businessman looking to protect himself
from the ups and downs of the business
and secure a guaranteed income
a working woman who wants to secure her
financial independence for the future or
simply someone planning for their
retirement
this plan would be great for you
[Music]
it is also an ideal gift option for
those who wish to ensure the financial
freedom of their parents spouse or
anyone else in their family
with the icici proof guaranteed pension
plan immediate annuity option
you can invest once and start getting
income from the next month itself
this plan allows you to lock in your
future payouts with a single investment
made today
let's understand how the plan works with
an example
mr sharma is a 50 year old married
businessman his wife is 45 years old and
they have a young daughter
although he earns well currently mr
sharma knows that business comes with a
lot of risk and revenue is impacted by a
number of external factors he has some
savings accumulated but is looking for a
plan that would help him get a regular
income and ensure financial security for
him and his family at all times he
decides to purchase the icici pro
guaranteed pension plan immediate
annuity online he makes a one-time
payment of rupees 25 lakhs
a large investment helps him get a
higher interest rate
mr sharma chooses to get monthly payouts
and selects the me joint life and
nominee option with his wife as his
joint life and his daughter as the
nominee he decides to go for the joint
life with return of purchase price
option
he starts receiving an income of rupees
12 200 from the next month itself this
will be paid to him as long as he lives
and will continue to be paid to his wife
after him when both the annuitants pass
away the purchase price would be
returned to the nominee this way he will
be able to leave behind a legacy for his
daughter the returns from this plan are
fixed and risk-free irrespective of
unpredictable market scenarios and
unstable interest rates
that's not all this plan also gives you
tax benefits on the premium paid under
section 80 ccc
with icici pro guaranteed pension plan
immediate annuity you can get multiple
benefits from a single plan making it an
essential component of everyone's
financial portfolio
you can buy the plan easily and securely
from the comfort of your home
buying online also comes with the
benefit of one percent additional
annuity amount payment can be made
through a range of online options
including net banking debit and credit
cards payment wallets and upi
your guaranteed income gets credited
directly to your bank account making the
plan completely safe and hassle free so
what are you waiting for
visit icici prolife.com and ensure
lifetime financial security for yourself
in just a few clicks
you can also consult our insurance
experts for free at 0-26-295-5609
[Music]